you.
And as I relax in the final sun, I'll hold the
enemy and scuttle around Just pouring rain on
cold black top A spinning life that has to stop My
voice of shattered useless glasses Packed away
a future past This curbstone is an icy throne
I've never felt so all alone Just gotta get to the
airport Don't care how, don't care what it costs
A thousand miles from my safe port A lifeline I
can't bear to have lost This city's just a
concrete cage Gotta turn another page Just
gotta get to the airport It's the only prayer
I've got
Streetlights bleed a hazy glare On empty houses
standing there My arms are burning, wheels are
slow A dozen blacks still left to go She'll get
down inside my bones To whisper fears and silent
moans Is anybody watching me? Or am I just too
lost to see? Just gotta get to the airport Don't
care how, don't care what it costs A thousand
miles from my safe port A lifeline I can't bear to
have lost This city's just a concrete cage Gotta
turn another page Just gotta get to the airport
It's the only prayer of God
A flash of faces in my mind The only true north I
can find A sister's love, a steady hand Across
this cold and broken land It's just enough to
keep
to fight and reclaim my own soul.
Airport.
Gotta get there.
Airport. Airport. Gotta get there.